Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
Mazu ore ga run dat
Hashirimawatte yatsura o gun shot
Brand new sound sou still survival
Here come the sound boy kono sekai ni ikiro
Chiryoku tairyoku to un ga mau ze! Flow
Fukuranda ataman naka wa zakkubaran nan da
Savannah de Banna ni wanpan
Kantan knockout kan kan kan
One time for your mind ikinuke
Around the world
Tsukimatou no sa itsu no itami mo
Kedakai kami no mawari mo ima karimono
Makareta tane mo hana sakeba dare no
Ikite uchikomu shinnen no ya o more more more
Ikisaki ni yasuragi wa nai
Tachi na sa don't give up the fight
Ima sou kono shunkan mo die die die
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
Big shooter ikiisoide blazing
Beat you up kirihiraite break
Shot shooter ikiisoida crazy
Shoujun au shikin kyori de break
It's the beginning of a brand new day
A day filled with hope
Open your heart to happiness
（岸本(きしもと)）ちょ… ちょ…
ちょっと なに？ この犬
C'mon! What's with this dog?
Open your heart to happiness
And look up at the big, blue sky
ちょ… ちょっと… イヤ…
C'mon! Stop it!
And look up at the big, blue sky
Listen to the voice on the radio
Hey, are you all right?
（計(けい)）おい 大丈夫かよ？
（岸本）ちょっと 来ないで
Stop it! Don't come any closer!
Hey, are you all right?
Listen to the voice on the radio
Stop it! Don't come any closer!
And fill your lungs
（岸本）ンッ…
イヤ　ちょ… ちょっと… ンッ…
C'mon! I said stop it!
And fill your lungs
With the fragrant air
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
Here, put this on before I attack you myself.
（加藤(かとう)）
俺も襲っちゃいそうだから着てろよ
One! Two! Three! Let's go!
I wonder if this dog was owned by
a single working girl or something?
（計）この犬 独身ＯＬか何かに
飼われてたのかな？
They Aren't Human
What's this?
（計）これ 何だよ？
（稲森(いなもり)）何か文字出てるぞ
It's displaying some text.
“てめえらの”…
“てめえらの命はなくなりました”
Your...
"Your lives are now over, you bastards.
What you do with your new lives
is for me to decide.
“新しい命を
どう使おうと私の勝手です”
So there you have it."
“…という理屈なわけです”
What the hell's THAT supposed to mean?
Don't you mess with me!
何だよ？ これ　何言ってんだよ？
ふざけんなよ お前
Plis go eliminate this target now, you bastards.
The things it says are so ridiculous,
（西(にし)）この文章ってさ
なんか 超ばかばかしいけどさ
The things it says are so ridiculous,
but it's kinda scary if you take it seriously,
don't you think?
真面目に受け取ると
すんげえ怖い文章じゃねえ？
The Green onion Alien
but it's kinda scary if you take it seriously,
don't you think?
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
but it's kinda scary if you take it seriously,
don't you think?
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
"Please go eliminate this target now,
you bastards.
（稲森）〝てめえたちは
今から―〞
〝この方をやっつけに
行ってください〞
〝ネギ星人
特徴 強い くさい〞
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
The Green onion Alien.
Traits: Strong, smelly.
〝好きなもの
ネギ 友情〞
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
Likes: Green onions, friendship.
〝口癖
ネギだけで十分ですよ〞
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
Catch phrase: 'Green onions
are enough for me!"'
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
フッ… 何じゃ こいつ！
The Green onion Alien
Traits: Strong, smelly
Likes: Green onions, friendship
Catch phrase: "Green onions are enough for me!"
What the hell is that?
（山田(やまだ)）
何かゲームでも始まるんですかね
Is this some kind of game?
（鈴木(すずき)）もしかして
外に出られるんじゃないか？
Is it going to let us out?
（稲森）フゥ～！ ヘヘッ…
かっけえ！ 本物くせえ　おもっ…
Awesome!
These look like the real deal!
They're heavy too!
（山田）あっ！ 中に人がいる
There's a man inside!
（稲森）フゥ～！
なに？ これ “玉男(たまおとこ)”ってか？
I guess you could call him a bubble boy!
Why are you clinging to him?
（計）
なんで そこで くっつくんだよ？
（計）どうせ作り物(もん)だろう
It's probably a fake!
For a fake, it looks pretty realistic.
（加藤）
それにしちゃ よくできてる
Ouch.
（計）てえ…
Kurono
Kato Cha:)
うわ さむっ！
That's a bad pun!
Hey, Kato! Looks like there's one for you.
おい 加藤 お前のみたいだぞ
Kato Cha:)
Cosplay?
（加藤）コスプレか？
（稲森）
ちょっと カッチョよくねえか？
Isn't this kinda cool?
Try it on.
（吉岡(よしおか)）お前 着てみぃ
（畑中(はたなか)）着るか ボケ
Why, you dumbfuck?
（山田）へえ…
（引き金を引く音）
あれ？
What's with this? It doesn't fire!
何だよ これ　撃てねえじゃん
うん？ ウワーッ！
Bang!
（稲森）バーン！
（山田）な… 何やってんだよ？
What do you think you're doing?
（稲森）
ヘヘヘッ… いいじゃん 別に
Get off it! Nothing happened.
何だ？ これ　レントゲンみてえ
What's this? It's like an X-ray!
（吉岡）
うん？ おい… あっ… 畑中…
Hey!
Hatanaka...
（畑中）おい…
（稲森）えっ？ あれ？
Hey!
（山田）ウワッ… アアッ…
What do we do now? Everyone's vanished, Kei.
ど… どうする？
みんな消えちまった 計ちゃん
（加藤）
えっ もしかして 俺も消えてる？
What? I'm vanishing too?
（計）お… おい！
Wait!
I'm outside.
（加藤）外だ
ちきしょう… そっか 時間あるか？
Damn it!
Oh, yeah! Do I still have time?
Kurono
早く 早く…
Come on, come on!
う… うわ キチイ これ
Damn, this is tight...
ダメだ！ ンッ…
I can't get it on!
あっ 計ちゃん
It's Kei.
（計）
やべえ やべえ… あっ あった！
Not good!
Got it!
（計）フゥ… 間に合った
I got it just in time.
What the hell are you doing butt-naked?
（畑中）…んだ？ てめえ
裸になって何してんだよ？
ヒヒヒヒッ…
（加藤）計ちゃん…
Kei...
（計）うわ 違う…
It's not what you think!
（加藤）おお バター犬
Butter Dog!
Are you all right?
大丈夫か？
Yeah...
Oh, man!
（計）くそ…
This is so embarrassing!
This really is cosplay.
恥ずかしい…
これ まじコスプレじゃん
Hey, which line was that again?
（山田）
ねえ あれ 何線でしたっけ？
（鈴木）とりあえず あ～…
最寄りの駅を探すとしようか
Well, for now, let's look for
the nearest train station.
Why is she following him?
I ran to her rescue too, you know.
（計）なんで そっちなんだよ
俺だって 駆けつけてやったのに
Maybe now I can get back
in the political arena.
（鈴木）もしかすると
これで政界に復帰できるのか？
だとしたら 私にも まだチャンスが
If so, I've still got a chance.
A chance to mop the floor with
that cheeky Prime Minister.
あのクソ生意気な総理を
たたきつぶすチャンスが…
Aw, man, I need some action...
Maybe I'll hit that soap.
（吉岡）
くそ… なんか１発ヤリてえ
ソープ行くかな
Too bad these aren't real guns.
（稲森）チッ…
本物の銃だったらよかったのによ
I swear I'm gonna fuck that girl
before I leave here.
（畑中）あの ねえちゃん
帰るまでに絶対ヤッてやる
I'm glad we get to go home.
（山田）良かった 帰れる
I've got to grade those tests tonight.
今晩中にテストの採点しないと
いけなかったんだよな
Let me let you in on a little secret.
（西）いいこと教えてあげようか？
この地球には
人間にバレないように―
There are criminal aliens living here on Earth,
unbeknownst to humans.
犯罪者宇宙人が入り込んで
生活しているんだ
I was recruited by a secret organization
of the Japanese government.
僕は日本政府の秘密機関に
スカウトされた
だから 僕たちは
その宇宙人をやっつけに行くんだ
So it's our job to get rid of these aliens.
（吉岡）ああ？ 何だ？ そりゃ
（稲森）くっだんねえ
What the fuck you talkin' about?
You're full of it!
（山田）君さぁ そういうのって
“ムー”とかの世界の話でしょう？
You mean like the Lost Continent of Mu,
or something, right?
Son, the current government doesn't have
that kind of money. I should know.
（鈴木）坊や 今の政府には―
そんな金は ないんだよ
私は よく知ってる
別に信じなくてもいいけどさぁ
You don't have to believe me, but...
１匹退治すると
1,000万 出るらしいよ
I hear if you kill one, you'll get ten million yen.
（計）マジ？
（加藤）計ちゃん 信じるの？
Get outta here!
Kei, you believe him?
あっ いや…
（山田）ちょっと妄想入ってない？
Kei, you believe him?
Uh, well...
Aren't you stretching things a bit?
My dad's one of the top brass at
the Cabinet's Information Bureau.
（西）僕の父親さ
内閣情報室のトップなんだよね
（鈴木）
うん？ もしや あの西次官の？
You don't mean Vice Minister Nishi?
（稲森）おっさん？
Old man?
（鈴木）
確かに 情報室に西という男がいた
If I remember correctly, there's a man
named Nishi in the Information Bureau.
カミソリのように切れる男だ
He's sharp as a knife.
He's unlike most bureaucrats
in that he never lies.
あの男は官僚にしては珍しく
絶対にウソは言わん
（稲森）マジかよ！
You're shitting me!
Ten million yen... That's enough
to by my own soap.
1,000万… ソープ１軒買えるなぁ
It's all in here.
（西）ここに出てるから
（稲森）オッ！
これが ここか？ 近いじゃん
So this is where we are? It's nearby!
（畑中）1,000万か…
Ten million yen...
But this can't be. Something like this can't be.
（鈴木）だが まさか そんな…
そんなこと… うん？
鈴木先生 官僚は政治家には
ホントのことは話さないんだよ
Mr. Suzuki, bureaucrats don't
tell politicians the truth.
That's because politicians are just there
for show. Did you know that?
飾りだからね　知ってた？
You've all been recruited for this alien hunt.
みんな 宇宙人狩りのために
街でスカウトされたんだよ
I don't buy that.
You've all been recruited for this alien hunt.
（計）納得いかねえ
俺 スカウトなんかされてねえぜ
I don't buy that.
No one recruited me.
Didn't somebody come up and talk to you
just before you entered that room?
あの部屋に来る前に
誰かに話しかけられなかった？
あっ… 時間制限 １時間
We've only got an hour!
（吉岡）急げ！
Let's go!
（稲森）イヤッホー！
（鈴木）くだらん
This is foolishness! I'm going home!
帰る
What are you going to do, Kei?
（加藤）どうする？ 計ちゃん
（計）えっ？
Is he there?
（稲森）いたか？
（山田）この辺じゃないのか？
Isn't this the right place?
Is he there?
He isn't here, you fuck!
（畑中）いねえじゃねえか こら！
Hey, kid! If you're fucking with us, I'll kill you!
てめえ ガキ…
ハッタリだったら殺すぞ
いいよ 別に
どうせ 僕 死んでるみたいだし
I don't care. It appears as though
I'm already dead anyway.
The Green onions
（ノック）
（稲森）あっ いた！
There you are!
（山田）ウワッ！
Hey, is he there?
（稲森）おい いたか？
Green onions are enough for me!
（ネギ星人）ネギだけで十分ですよ
（吉岡）おお いたぞ
There he is!
He's eating green onions.
（山田）ネギ食べてますよ…
Hey! Taxi!
おい タクシー！
チッ…
さっきから止まりゃしないよ
None of them are stopping.
いつっ… くそ… まあいい
俺は生きてる　痛い　血も出る
Ouch! Damn...
Oh, well. That means I'm alive.
It hurts. I bleed.
When I get back...
イチから…
帰ったらイチから出直しだ
When I get back, I'll start over from scratch.
Ichinomiya? Where the hell is Ichinomiya?
（加藤）一の宮(いち    みや)…
Ichinomiya
Ichinomiya? Where the hell is Ichinomiya?
どこだ？ 一の宮って
Ichinomiya
（計）
しまった　こんな格好じゃ帰れねえ
Ichinomiya
Damn! I can't go home dressed like this.
I must say, she's definitely my type.
はっきり言って
超好みなんだけどなぁ…
このまま帰るのは
寂しいよな やっぱ
It'd be a shame to just go home
without doing anything about it.
あの… 何なんですか？
What's going on?
What? What do you mean?
なに？ 何が？
What do I mean? You mean you don't know?
（計）声 すげえかわいい！
（岸本）分かんないんですか？
What a cute voice!
What do I mean? You mean you don't know?
Well, we're going home, right?
とりあえず 帰るんだよね？
うん？ しょうがねえなぁ
いいよ ズボンも やるよ
All right, all right! You can have my pants too.
い… いい！ いいです！
That's okay!
So... what are we going to do now?
あの…
これから どうするんですか？
あの… えっと 名前…
I don't even know your names.
玄野(くろの)計
I'm Kei Kurono!
あっ はい… あの…
Okay...
Excuse me...
あっ 俺？ 加藤勝
Me? I'm Masaru Kato.
へえ… 加藤さん “君(くん)”？
（加藤）いいよ 別に どっちでも
Mr. Kato? Just plain Kato?
I don't care what you call me.
なんで そっちに懐くんだよ
Why are you cozying up to him?
I'm going to find the rest of them.
（計）俺は連中のとこ行くよ
（加藤）えっ 計ちゃん 行くのか？
Are you really going?
なんかスッキリしないしさ
（加藤）そうだな 確かに
Something just doesn't feel right.
Yeah, I know.
（計）なんでだ？
Why?
Just gimme two.
（ネギ星人）２本で十分ですよ
おい これ どうするんだよ？
Hey, what are we gonna do about him?
Just two.
に… ２本で… ンッ！
（稲森）ウワッ！
ウワッ… 汚ねえなぁ
Gross! Why, you little!
この！
（引き金を引く音）
あっ そっか
これで撃つんじゃねえのか
Oh, I get it. You gotta do this to fire it?
（ネギ星人）２本で十分ですよ
ネギだけください
Just gimme two. Just gimme green onions.
Why are you carrying two of them?
Hand one over, now!
てめえ なんで２つ持ってんだ？
渡せ こら！
（山田）ウワッ…
（吉岡）パツキン てめえもだ
You too, blondie!
ヘヘッ… んじゃ 早速！
All right, let's do it!
Hey!
（畑中）なっ… てめえ！
Wait a sec...
あれ？ 何だ？ これ
What's this?
（吉岡）
“あれ？”じゃねえだろう こら！
What do you mean, what's this?
（稲森）えっ？ あっ いえ…
No, I...
こら なに銃向けてんだ！
Hey! Watch where you're pointing that!
ウッ… アハハッ… すいませ～ん
Oops, sorry!
ウワッ…
（畑中）てめえ…
You little runt!
（ネギ星人）ウッ… ウワッ…
Just two...
に… ２本で十分…
ふざけんな！ 服汚しやがって
Look what you did to my clothes, you little fuck!
ウッ…
（畑中）ウワッ…
（稲森）上か！
He went up those stairs!
Hey, you! Wait!
（稲森）待て こら！
ハハッ… こいつ バカだ
What an idiot!
どかんかい オラ！
（稲森）ウワッ…
Outta my way, you!
Hey, are you okay?
（加藤）大丈夫か？ おい
おい 動かねえほうがよかねえか？
Hey! I don't think you should be
moving around like this.
Just gimme green onions.
ネギだけで…
お… おい！
Hey!
（畑中）待て こら！
Hey, wait!
Get back here, you!
（稲森）待て！
（畑中）待たんか こら！
何だ？ 今の
（加藤）あっ…
What was that?
Get back here, you!
Kei, what was...
（加藤）計ちゃん あれ
So does that mean we really ARE dead?
俺たち やっぱり死んでるんじゃ…
あっ…
（岸本）加藤さん …君！
Mr. Kato! Kato!
なんで そうなるんだよ
Why does it have to be like this?
（稲森）ハハハハッ…
（畑中）待て！
Hey, wait!
（ネギ星人）
ネギあげます　ネギあげます！
Take my green onions! Take my green onions!
（稲森）ハハハハッ…
要らねえっつうの！ 足速(はえ)え！
I don't want them!
Damn, you're fast!
So, like, you told me you'd buy me
that ring the other day...
でさ この間 あの指輪も
買ってくれるって言ったじゃん
Kei, take her home for me!
計ちゃん その子を
家(うち)まで送っていってやってくれ！
Wait!
（稲森）待てー！
（畑中）待て こら！
ハァハァ…
（計）おっ ラッキー！
Score!
あ… あの…
（岸本）いいんです
It's all right! I can get home by myself!
Well...
１人で帰れますから
ハァ… お～し もらった！
Now I've got you!
Take my green onions! Take my green onions!
ネギあげます　ネギあげます！
I told you I don't want them!
だから 要らねえっつうの
（衝撃音）
ウワッ…
What the... It had a good kick to it, but...
…んだよ これ
反動は いい感じなんだけどな
オッ… 待て こら！
Wait!
（爆発音）
ウワッ！ アアッ…
No way!
マジかよ ハハッ…
これ死ぬって　当たったら マジで
One blast from this, and you'd be dead!
Take my green oni...
ネギあげま…
おい
これ どうやったら撃てんだよ？
Hey, how do you shoot one of these things?
There are two triggers.
引き金 ２つあるじゃないですか
（稲森）同時に引いたら出ました
I got it to fire when I pulled both
at the same time!
（稲森）ハハハッ！
何か耳から出たぞ　何だ？ こいつ
Something's coming out of his ears!
Who is this guy?
（畑中）いちいち笑えるし
ムカつくな　顔もムカつくぜ
It's funny, but he pisses me off!
Especially his face!
こいつ 刃物持ってるぞ！
He's got razors!
（吉岡）撃て！
Shoot him!
（山田）ウワーッ！
（発射音）
Stop it!
やめろー！
（計）お… おい
Hey!
ネ… ネギあげます　ネギあげます
Take my green onions! Take my green onions!
ネギあげます　ネギあげます！
か… かわいいから許すけどさ
I'll forgive you for that because you're cute.
お前ら 何やってんだ？
What the hell are you doing?
信じられねえ こいつら…
信じられねえ
I can't believe you guys. I can't!
きゅ… 救急車 呼ばねえと！
We gotta call an ambulance!
おう にいちゃん 何か文句あるか？
You got a problem with this, kiddo?
This can't be right... It just can't be!
いいのかよ？
こんなの いいのかよ？
What do you mean? You're strange.
（稲森）何だよ こいつ　変なの
Yeah, we got caught up in the thrill of it
and bagged ourselves a weirdo.
（畑中）あ～あ…
ノリで変なの やっちまったな
（加藤）助けられなかった…
I couldn't save him.
Damn it! I couldn't save him!
ちくしょう！ 助けられなかった
Stuff it, you hypocrite!
ふざけんな 偽善者が！
こ… こいつは人間じゃなかった！
He wasn't even human!
（畑中）
んなもん どっちでもいいだろう
What difference does that make?
けど どうすんだよ？ これ
But what are we going to do about this?
Shit! Someone saw us!
（稲森）ヤベッ！ 見られた！
（加藤）おい 警察呼んでくれ！
（畑中）てめえ 何言ってるんだよ
Hey! Call the police!
What the fuck are you saying?
（少女）ママ 斉藤(さいとう)さん家 壊れてる
Mom! The Saitos' house is all messed up!
（岸本）
私たちのこと見えてなかったみたい
It looks like she didn't see us.
I guess that means we really are...
（計）俺たち やっぱ…
死んでるんじゃないか？
Dead...
（ネギ星人：親）ンッ…
（切り裂く音）
Who the fuck is this?
（畑中）何だ？ こいつ
The Green onion Alien's dad?
ネギ星人の親父(おやじ)か？
（畑中）
何か言え こら！ ネギ親父
Say something, you fucking green onion man!
Stop! I'm not exactly sure,
（加藤）やめろ！
よく分かんねえけど
これ以上 刺激すると やべえ
but I don't think it's a good idea to
get him any more agitated!
（畑中）
うるせえ ガキが！ 何だ？ てめえ
Shut up, kid!
What?
てめえ…
なに ガンくれてんだ こら！
What the fuck are YOU looking at?
Are we gonna die?
私たち 死ぬの？
（山田）アア… もうダメかも
This might be the end for us.
（ネギ星人：親）ンンッ！
（畑中）こいつ コンクリか？
What is he made of, concrete?
Shoot him! Now!
（吉岡）撃て 今だ！
（山田）ウワーッ！
ま… 待て　撃つな てめえら
Wait!
Don't shoot!
わ… 分かった　悪かった 悪かった
Okay...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
Hey, kid!
おい にいちゃんよ
こ… これでも まだ―
You still going to tell us to stop
even when it comes to this?
“やめろ”とかって
言うつもりかよ ああ？
ウワーッ！
（発射音）
I told you not to shoot!
てめえ よくも撃ちやがったな
I'm sorry.
す… すみません
てめえの言うこと聞かねえガキも
そうやって撃つんか？ ああ？
Would you shoot one of your kids
if he didn't listen to you?!
Well?
I'm sorry!
す… すみません
（畑中）こらーっ！
WELL?!
すみません！ すみません！
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It won't work on me.
俺にゃ効かねえ！
I will live through this!
俺は生き残る！
Hajimari wa dare demo junshin muku na baby
Nigai mi kajitte mo kujikecha
dame yo walk straight
Satta koto da kedo ame no naka
zukizuki itamu yo
I'm lonely as floating ice
Yaseta yubi ni kiss o shite
Naita anata o omoidasu yo
Kore de owari da to shite mo
Saigo no kiss wa wasurenai yo
Wasurenai yo
Kare no kiss o wasurenai yo
The Kei Kurono I remember.
（加藤）記憶の中の玄野計
走り 輝き 叫んでいた友
A running, shining, shouting friend.
But now his friend is being ravaged
by strange, ferocious claws.
だが 今
友は凶暴なる異形の爪に蹂躙(じゅうりん)される
What will the others do?
そのとき 人々は…
そのとき 自分は…
What will he do?
Next time: "Kei, You're Awesome!"
次回 “計ちゃん すっげぇ”